[
  {
    "id": "q0001",
    "question": "feel for",
    "answer": "search by touch"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0002",
    "question": "pluck up courage",
    "answer": "common & idiomatic expression describing the act of summoning courage and strength to do sth difficult or frightening."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0003",
    "question": "take a back seat",
    "answer": "to allow others to take the lead or be in control"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0004",
    "question": "take the bull by the horns",
    "answer": "to confront a difficult situation directly and with determination"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0005",
    "question": "take the plunge",
    "answer": "to make a decision to do something risky or uncertain"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0006",
    "question": "came face to face with danger",
    "answer": "to confront or encounter sth threatening directly"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0007",
    "question": "decided on the spur of the moment",
    "answer": "to make a quick decision without much thought or planning; she decided on her brother's favourite"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0008",
    "question": "show someone the ropes",
    "answer": "to teach someone how to do a job or task"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0009",
    "question": "as fast as his legs could carry him",
    "answer": "to run as quickly as possible. emphasize urgency and maximum effort"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0010",
    "question": "took to his heels",
    "answer": "to run away quickly esp facing danger or trouble"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0011",
    "question": "take the law into one's own hands",
    "answer": "to take action to enforce the law"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0012",
    "question": "take the wind out of one's sails",
    "answer": "to surprise or deflate someone by doing or saying something unexpected"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0013",
    "question": "bring to a boil",
    "answer": "to heat a liquid until it reaches the boiling point"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0014",
    "question": "bring to a head",
    "answer": "to cause a situation to reach a critical point"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0015",
    "question": "defy all odds",
    "answer": "to succeed despite facing significant challenges or obstacles"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0016",
    "question": "stifle a yawn",
    "answer": "to suppress or hold back a yawn"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0017",
    "question": "cut out",
    "answer": "to remove or eliminate; removal by cutting; Ceasing or stopping an action or process"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0018",
    "question": "cut out for",
    "answer": "to be suited or qualified for a particular task or role"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0019",
    "question": "throw a tantrum",
    "answer": "to have an angry outburst or display of frustration typically by a child"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0020",
    "question": "throw a spanner in the works",
    "answer": "to cause a problem or complication that disrupts a plan or process"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0021",
    "question": "ahead of the curve",
    "answer": "to be more advanced or innovative than others"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0022",
    "question": "face the facts",
    "answer": "accept a hard truth or reality even if it is unpleasant"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0023",
    "question": "washed up on the shore",
    "answer": "fixed expression: carried by wave onto land when a thing is dead or weak"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0024",
    "question": "put on a brave front",
    "answer": "to pretend to be brave or confident in a difficult situation"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0025",
    "question": "put one's foot down",
    "answer": "to assert oneself firmly or insist on a particular course"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0026",
    "question": "distinguish A from B",
    "answer": "to tell the difference between A and B; vs seperate: physically move apart; doesn't tell the difference"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0027",
    "question": "look out for",
    "answer": "to be vigilant or watchful for something"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0028",
    "question": "hold one's weight",
    "answer": "contribute one's fair share to a task or effort. not relying on others to pick up the slack"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0029",
    "question": "hit the roof",
    "answer": "to become extremely angry or enraged"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0030",
    "question": "send for repairs",
    "answer": "general phrase used for fixing damage."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0031",
    "question": "easily accessible by public transport",
    "answer": "convenient to reach using public transportation."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0032",
    "question": "the situation is in hands",
    "answer": "in hand means under control or being managed effectively."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0033",
    "question": "the situation is in good hands",
    "answer": "means that it is being managed by someone capable or trustworthy."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0034",
    "question": "the situation is in flux",
    "answer": "means that it is uncertain or constantly changing."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0035",
    "question": "excuse ready at hand",
    "answer": "at hand means readily available or prepared in advanced."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0036",
    "question": "go on a raid",
    "answer": "fixed expression: to conduct a sudden attack or incursion into a place; \"ON\" is used when talking about organized actions or activities."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0037",
    "question": "decide for oneself",
    "answer": "idiom; emphasize decision is made independently or without external influence."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0038",
    "question": "decide by oneself",
    "answer": "\"by oneself\" emphasizes alone without help."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0039",
    "question": "observe silence",
    "answer": "to keep or maintain silence intentionally in formal or public setting (library,ceremony,moment of silence)."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0040",
    "question": "ring through the air",
    "answer": "standard phrase: to be heard clearly and distinctly in the air. e.g. \"a loud,clear and sharp sound \" echoing or traveling through space. often used for bells,screams,or gunshots. more vivid image of traveling in space comparing with pieceing."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0041",
    "question": "strike a match",
    "answer": "cause a match to burn by rubbing it against a hard rough surface"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0042",
    "question": "rummage through Cabinets and drawers",
    "answer": "to search through cabinets and drawers in a disorganized or haphazard manner"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0043",
    "question": "run errands",
    "answer": "to perform small tasks or chores,often outside the home"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0044",
    "question": "native to",
    "answer": "originating or naturally occurring in a particular place or environment."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0045",
    "question": "standing on one leg",
    "answer": "to balance on one leg,often used in exercises or physical activities"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0046",
    "question": "with more time on their hands",
    "answer": "having extra time available to do something"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0047",
    "question": "trial and error",
    "answer": "a method of problem-solving characterized by trying various solutions until finding one that works"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0048",
    "question": "come down on",
    "answer": "criticize or punish harshly someone for their actions or decisions"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0049",
    "question": "all proceeds are donated to",
    "answer": "all money raised or earned is given to a charity"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0050",
    "question": "a roof over one's head",
    "answer": "a place to live or shelter,often used in a metaphorical sense to refer to having a stable home or living situation"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0051",
    "question": "a way of giving back to the community / society",
    "answer": "a method or action that contributes positively to the local community or society"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0052",
    "question": "building blocks",
    "answer": "fundamental components or elements that are essential for creating or developing something larger or more complex"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0053",
    "question": "get that much deserved rest",
    "answer": "to finally receive the rest or relaxation that one has earned or needed"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0054",
    "question": "get a good night's sleep",
    "answer": "to have a restful and restorative sleep during the night"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0055",
    "question": "subject to",
    "answer": "likely to be affected by or experience something,often used in legal or formal contexts"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0056",
    "question": "tight deadline",
    "answer": "a deadline that is difficult to meet due to its short time frame or urgency"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0057",
    "question": "should...you",
    "answer": "should you decide to go to the park,I will join you."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0058",
    "question": "on one hand...on the other hand",
    "answer": "used to present two contrasting perspectives or options"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0059",
    "question": "accede to my request",
    "answer": "to agree to or accept my request,often after some persuasion or negotiation"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0060",
    "question": "object to my request",
    "answer": "to express disapproval or disagreement with my request"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0061",
    "question": "attribute to",
    "answer": "attribute to success to parent's unwaveing love and support,to regard something as being caused by or resulting from a particular source or factor"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0062",
    "question": "spend within your means",
    "answer": "to manage your finances in a way that does not exceed your available resources or budget."
  }
]